[
  {
    "question": "Author of The Divine Comedy",
    "answer": "Dante Alighieri"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of Don Quixote",
    "answer": "Miguel de Cervantes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of One Hundred Years of Solitude",
    "answer": "Gabriel García Márquez"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of The Tale of Genji",
    "answer": "Murasaki Shikibu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of The Stranger",
    "answer": "Albert Camus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of The Metamorphosis",
    "answer": "Franz Kafka"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of Things Fall Apart",
    "answer": "Chinua Achebe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of Crime and Punishment",
    "answer": "Fyodor Dostoevsky"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of The Brothers Karamazov",
    "answer": "Fyodor Dostoevsky"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of War and Peace",
    "answer": "Leo Tolstoy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of The Iliad",
    "answer": "Homer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of The Aeneid",
    "answer": "Virgil"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of The Rubáiyát",
    "answer": "Omar Khayyam"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of Faust",
    "answer": "Johann Wolfgang von Goethe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of The Kite Runner",
    "answer": "Khaled Hosseini"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of The Name of the Rose",
    "answer": "Umberto Eco"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of The Alchemist",
    "answer": "Paulo Coelho"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of Midnight’s Children",
    "answer": "Salman Rushdie"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of Invisible Man",
    "answer": "Ralph Ellison"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of The Canterbury Tales",
    "answer": "Geoffrey Chaucer"
  }
]
